Guide to the Records of Graham Windham 1804-2011 MS 2916
New-York Historical Society
- Series I - Orphan Asylum Society/Graham Home for Children, 1806-1981 (bulk 1806-1977)
  - Subseries I.9 - Visual Materials, circa 1910-1977
    The subseries contains three boxes, and two additional folders in an oversize box, containing primarily photographic prints, as well as a smaller quantity of negatives, contact sheets, mock-ups for annual reports and brochures, two loose pages from a photo album, one ink sketch, and some paper materials related to the photographs and interfiled with them.
    Subjects include children and activities at the OAS, benefits and other events, celebrity visitors, and annual report materials. Most photographs were created for publicity purposes or for internal documentation. Photographic formats include prints mounted on board or paper, many sizes of loose prints, and stereoscopic prints. Professional photographers represented in the collection include Alfred J. Merz and Daniel Berry, and there is one print by Lewis Hine. The materials were kept by the Development Department and were arranged by subject and date. Original folder titles have been maintained.
    The subseries also contains one box of wooden printing blocks with negative images used in OAS printed materials circa 1910-1950's, and one scrapbook/photograph album documenting Black Solidarity Week 1974. The printing blocks and the scrapbook are arranged at the end of the subseries.
    - Orphan Asylum on Riverside Drive before 1902 (reprint), undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 1)
    - At campus, circa 1902-1919 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 2)
    - Early Photos Campus, 1902-1920 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3)
    - Campus, circa 1918 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 4)
    - Campus Pony Cart, circa 1902-1920 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - Hastings Photos, circa 1902-1930 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - At Campus, circa 1920-1929 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 7)
    - Campus, circa 1930-1939 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 8)
    - At Campus, circa 1940-1949 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 9)
    - Campus Buildings, undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 10)
    - Campus 1950's, circa 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 11)
    - Administration Building with Children, 1956 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 12)
    - Campus 1960's, circa 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 13)
    - Miss Ehinger, circa 1925-1967 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 14)
    - JoAnn Ruggero, 1947 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 15)
    - Allen Thomas, Executive Director 1946-1965, circa 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 16)
    - Former Trustees, circa 1956-1960 and undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 17)
    - Various Activities, circa 1940-1949 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
    - Children and Buildings, 1952 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 2)
    - Various Activities, 1954 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)
    - Various Activities, 1955 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
    - Various Activities, 1956 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 5)
    - Various Activities, 1957 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6)
    - Various Activities, 1958 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 7)
    - Various Activities, 1959 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8)
    - Various Activities, 1960 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 9)
    - Various Activities, 1961 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 10)
    - Various Activities, 1962 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 11)
    - Various Activities, 1963 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 12)
    - Various Activities, 1968 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 13)
    - Various Activities, 1969 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 14)
    - Various Activities - Undated, circa 1920-1973 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 15)
    - Children with Eddie Fisher, 1956 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1)
    - Hollywood Visits, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 2)
    - Unidentifed Cowboy, 1956 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 3)
    - Hopalong Cassidy, 1955 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 4)
    - Paul Newman, 1961 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 5)
    - Bert Parks, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 6)
    - "Doc" Severinsen, 1969 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7)
    - Althea Gibson, 1970 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 8)
    - Swimming pool ground breaking and dedication, 1956 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 9)
    - IBM Photos, circa 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 10)
    - IBM negatives and contact sheets, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 11)
    - IBM negative, 1977 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 12)
    - Graham school aerial photos, 1963 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 13)
    - Children's Center, 1964 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 14)
    - Batchelor House, corca 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 15)
    - 149th and 150th Anniversary, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 16)
    - Benefit Photos - Boat Ride, 1956 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 17)
    - Benefit Photos - Boat Ride, 1957 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 18)
    - Benefit Photos - Theater, 1959 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 19)
    - Benefit Photos - Boat Ride, 1962 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 20)
    - Benefit Photos - Theater, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 21)
    - Benefit Photos - Dinner Dance, 1963 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 22)
    - Benefit Photos - Dinner Dance, 1965 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 23)
    - Benefit Photos - Dinner Dance, 1966 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 24)
    - Benefit Photos - Theater "Star Spangled Girls", 1967 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 25)
    - Benefit Photos - Dinner Dance, 1967 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 26)
    - Report with attached photos, and miscellaneous, circa 1954 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 1)
    - Polaroids and small prints - some with captions, 1964 and undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder 2)
    - Perkins Cottage 1977 Renovation (Offsite-box 23, Folder 3)
    - Hamilton Cottage Prints and Negatives, 1977 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report negatives, circa 1965 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report 1969 Ink Sketches of Grounds, Buildings (Offsite-box 23, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report Matted Prints, 1970 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report Photos and Matted Prints, 1973 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report Photos, notes, releases, circa 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting - negatives, 1977 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 10)
    - Description of Home - negative, undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder 11)
    - Lewis Hine photographic print, views of grounds, undated, circa 1920-1940 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 12)
    - Photo album pages, circa 1920-1940 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 13)
    - Portrait of boys wtih farm tools, circa 1930's (Box OS 1, Folder 3)
    - Mock-ups for brochure, circa 1950 (Box OS 1, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook/Photo Album: Black Solidarity Week, 1974 November 4-8 (Offsite-box 136, Volume 163)
    - Printing Blocks, circa 1910-1956 (Offsite-box OS 2)
  - Subseries I.10 - Clippings, circa 1853-1977
    Scope and content
    The subseries contains newspaper clippings and articles regarding the Graham School/Graham Home circa 1876-1977, and a set of bound copies of two periodicals from 1853-1856 --The Advocate and Guardian and The Child's Paper.
    Additional pre-merger Graham Home clippings may be found in Subseries III.8 (in volume 216), along with post-merger clippings. Windham clippings are in Subseries II.6.
    - Bound copies of The Advocate and Guardian Vol. XXI, No. 15 - Vol. XXII, No. 23 and The Child's Paper Vol. 2, No. 1 - Vol. 5, No. 11, 1853-1856 (Offsite-box 136, Volume 164)
    - Newspaper article re: a will, 1876 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 12)
    - New York Daily Tribune, 1884 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 13)
    - Time Magazine Graham History Article, 1956 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 14)
    - The Morning Call Editorial Page - GW 150th Anniversary, 1956 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 15)
    - Westchester Life article on the Graham School, 1956 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 16)
    - New York Times History of Graham, 1959 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1956, 1976, 1977 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 18)
    - "Graham: Home on the Hudson" reprint from Westchester County publishers daily newspapers, 1962 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 19)
    - The Scarsdale Inquirer: "Graham Home...Reflects Development in Social Welfare", 1962 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 20)
    - Clippings (photocopies), circa 1950-1969 (Offsite-box OS 3)
- Series II - Society for the Relief of Half-Orphans and Destitute Children/Windham Child Care, 1841-1977
  The Society for the Relief of Half-Orphan and Destitute Children (SRHO) was founded in 1835, and incorporated in 1837. In 1947, after moving and restructuring, it was renamed The Windham Society for the Care of Boys. In 1949, it merged with Protestant Children's Services, Inc., and was renamed Windham Children's Services. In 1969, it merged with the Child Care Center, an agency which had previously merged with the Tuberculosis Preventorium for Children, and became Windham Child Care. In 1977, the agency merged with The Graham Home for Children, and the combined entity became Graham-Windham Services to Families and Children (now Graham Windham).
  The series contains materials of the Society for the Relief of Half-Orphan and Destitute Children and its subsequent organizations from (1926?-1977), up to the merger with the Graham Home for Children. For records after the merger, see Series III.
  Materials include minutes, annual reports, and photographs.
  The Society for the Relief of Half-Orphan and Destitute Children was founded in 1835, and incorporated in 1837. In 1947, after moving and restructuring, it was renamed The Windham Society for the Care of Boys. In 1949, it merged with Protestant Children's Services, Inc., and was renamed Windham Children's Services. In 1969, it merged with the Child Care Center, an agency which had previously merged with the Tuberculosis Preventorium for Children, and became Windham Child Care. In 1977, the agency merged with The Graham Home for Children, and the combined entity became Graham-Windham Services to Families and Children (now Graham Windham).
  The series contains Minutes of the Society for the Relief of Half-Orphan and Destitute Children and its subsequent organizations from 1923-1977, up to the merger with the Graham Home for Children. Minutes from 1933-1945 are missing. Minutes prior to 1923 may be found at the Butler Library, Columbia University.
  The series also includes Annual Reports 1868-1979 (not inclusive) in loose copies and bound volumes, a pamphlet memorializing founder Eliza Tomlinson (1862), three folders of administrative documents (1926-1976), a scrapbook of newspaper clippings (1957-1964) and a set of photographs of celebrities, autographed for the Windham children (1965 and undated).
  For records after the merger with the Graham Home for Children, see Series III. For records of the Tuberculosis Preventorium for Children, see Series IV.
  The series is arranged in 6 subseries, as follows:
  II.1 - Board Minutes, 1923-1977
  II.2 - Committee Minutes, 1841-1968
  II.3 - Annual Reports, 1853-1973
  II.4 - Administrative and Printed Documents, 1862-1976
  II.5 - Photographs, 1965 and undated
  II.6 - Clippings, 1957-1964
  - Subseries II.1 - Board Minutes, 1923-1977
    The series contains Minutes of the Society for the Relief of Half-Orphan and Destitute Children and its subsequent organizations (Windham Society for the Care of Boys, Windham Children's Services, Windham Child Care) from 1923-1977, up to the merger with the Graham Home for Children. Minutes from 1933-1945 are missing. Minutes prior to 1923 may be found at the Butler Library, Columbia University.
    An index to the minutes is available to researchers at the New-York Historical Society manuscript department.
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1923 January - 1926 June (Offsite-box 134, Volume 165)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1926 October - 1932 December (Offsite-box 24, Folder 1)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1945 October - 1948 January (Offsite-box 24, Folder 2)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1948 March - 1949 May (Offsite-box 137, Volume 166)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1949 September - 1950 November (Offsite-box 137, Volume 167)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1951 January - 1954 November (Offsite-box 137, Volume 168)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1955 January - 1958 December (Offsite-box 137, Volume 169)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1959 January - 1962 November (Offsite-box 138, Volume 170)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1963 January - 1965 November (Offsite-box 138, Volume 171)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1966 January - 1968 November (Offsite-box 138, Volume 172)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1969 January - 1971 June (Offsite-box 138, Volume 173)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1971 September - 1973 March (Offsite-box 139, Volume 174)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1973 April - 1975 April (Offsite-box 139, Volume 175)
    - SRHO Board Minutes, 1975 May - 1977 June (Offsite-box 139, Volume 176)
    - Reports of the Executive Director to the Board 1950-1962, and Board Minutes 1965, 1950-1965 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 3)
  - Subseries II.2 - Committee Minutes, 1841-1968
    The subseries contains 3 bound volumes of minutes of committees.
    - Minutes of the Visiting Committee, 1841-1845 (Offsite-box 139, Volume 177)
    - Children's Service Committee Minutes, 1959-1968 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 178)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 179)
  - Subseries II.3 - Annual Reports, 1853-1973
    The subseries consists of Annual Reports of the Society for the Relief of Half Orphans and Destitute Children, bound together in volumes, 1853-1937, and loose copies of Annual Reports of the organization 1868-1949 and its successor organization, Windham Children's Service, 1964-1973 (not inclusive).
    An index to the annual reports is available to researchers at the New-York Historical Society manuscript department.
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1853-1863 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 180)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1864-1874 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 181)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1875-1886 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 182)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1886-1898 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 183)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1897-1909 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 184)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1910-1923 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 185)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1924-1933 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 186)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1934-1937 (Offsite-box 140, Volume 187)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1868-1900 (Offsite-box 25)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1900-1919 (Offsite-box 26)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1919-1934 (Offsite-box 27)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1934-1936 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 2)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1939-1941 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1942-1945 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1946-1947 and 1949 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 5)
    - SRHO Annual Reports, 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 6)
  - Subseries II.4 - Administrative and Printed Documents, 1862-1976, 1872-1976
    The subseries includes a pamphlet memorializing founder Eliza Tomlinson (1862), and three folders of administrative documents (1926-1976).
    The pamphlet in Folder 1 is available for research. Folders 2, 3, and 4 are closed to the public for a term of one hundred years from date of creation. Documents older than one hundred years are open for research.
    - Eliza Tomlinson memorial pamphlet, 1862 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 7)
    - Visitor's Notes, circa 1926 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 8)
    - Audits, 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 9)
    - Board members' manual, 1976 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 10)
  - Subseries II.5 - Photographs, 1965 and undated
    The subseries includes autographed original photographs of President Dwight D. Eisenhower, President Harry Truman, Mayor Robert Wagner, Adlai Stevenson, Leonard Bernstein, Danny Kaye, Emmett Kelly, and Elizabeth Arden, most signed "to the Windham Children." These photographs had been framed and displayed by the Windham agency, but have now been removed from their frames for conservation purposes. Researchers may view photocopies of these signed portraits, not the originals.
    The subseries does not include photographs of the Windham Agency. However, a few photographs from the agency before its merger with the Graham Home may be found arranged with post-merger photographs in Box 89, Folder 6 of Series III.9.
    - Signed Photographs, 1965 and undated (Offsite-box 28, Folder 11)
    - Signed photograph of Adlai Stevenson, undated (Box OS 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries II.6 - Clippings, 1957-1964
    - Windham Clippings Scrapbook, 1957-1964 (Offsite-box 136, Volume 188)
- Series III - Graham Windham, 1970-2011 (bulk 1977-2010)
  Series III contains records of Graham Windham from 1977-2010, after the merger of two predecessor organizations, the Graham and Windham agencies. For records of the predecessor organizations, see Series I and II.
  The series contains Minutes of the Board of Trustees and various committees; annual reports; records from the office of President Joyce LePenn; school records including yearbooks; printed materials and other records kept by the Development Office; photographs, photograph albums, and clippings.
  Series III contains records of the Graham Windham childcare agency from 1977-2010, after the merger of two predecessor organizations, the Graham and Windham agencies. For records of the predecessor organizations, see Series I and II. Records of the agency open to the public include printed matter such as annual reports, brochures, flyers, programs, newsletters, yearbooks, newspaper and magazine articles, photographs and portraits from any date. All other material, including minutes, president's records, school records, and any other administrative documents are closed to the public for a period of 100 years from the date of their creation. The series contains Minutes of the Board of Trustees and various committees; annual reports; records from the office of President Joyce Lapenn; school records including yearbooks; printed materials and other records kept by the Development Office; photographs, photograph albums, and clippings. It is arranged in ten subseries as follows:
  III.1 - Board Minutes, 1977-2000
  III.2 - Committee Minutes, 1982-2000
  III.3 - Annual Reports, 1977-2006
  III.4 - Office of President Joyce LaPenn, 1989-1996
  III.5 - Records of the Greenburg-Graham School District, 1970-2009
  III.6 - Office of Development - Printed Matter, circa 1977-2011
  III.7 - Office of Development - Administrative Materials, 1983-2011 (bulk 1990-1996)
  III.8 - Office of Development - Press Releases, Articles and Clippings, 1975-2010
  III.9 - Photographic Materials, circa 1978-2010
  III.10 - Artifacts, 1986-2002
  - Subseries III.1 - Board Minutes, 1977-2000
    The subseries contains 6 bound volumes of minutes of meetings of the Graham-Windham Board of Directors, 1977-2000, followed by 4 boxes of board minutes and related materials 1983-1999.
    The boxed material includes duplicates of the minutes in the bound volumes, as well as related material not found in the volumes. The boxed material may have been kept by the Development Department or another department. Original folder titles have been retained. Minutes from 1982 September - 1983 October are not in a bound volume, but may be found in box 29.
    Records in this subseries are closed to the public for a period of 100 years from the date of their creation.
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1977 September - 1979 December (Offsite-box 141, Volume 189)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1980 January - 1982 July (Offsite-box 141, Volume 190)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1983 September - 1986 October (Offsite-box 141, Volume 191)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1987 January - 1991 March (Offsite-box 142, Volume 192)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1991 May - 1995 June (Offsite-box 142, Volume 193)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1995 September - 2000 December (Offsite-box 142, Volume 194)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1982 September - 1983 October (Offsite-box 29, Folder 1)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 2)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 3)
    - Graham-Windham Board Minutes, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting Agenda and Miscellaneous including Speeches, 1990 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 5)
    - Board Meeting Invitees, 1991 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting Miscellaneous and Speeches, 1991 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Monthly Reports, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 8)
    - Board Minutes, 1991-1994 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting Speeches and Miscellaneous, 1993 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting Correspondence, 1993 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting Invitation, 1993 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, 1994 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, 1996 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 1)
    - Board Meeting Scripts, 1996 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 2)
    - Board Minutes, 1996 January - November (Offsite-box 31, Folder 3)
    - Board Minutes, 1996 September 17 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 4)
    - Board Minutes, 1996 November 19 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 5)
    - Board Minutes, 1997 January - November (Offsite-box 31, Folder 6)
    - Board Meeting, 1997 January - November (Offsite-box 31, Folder 7)
    - Board Minutes, 1997 March 18 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 8)
    - Board Minutes, 1997 May 20 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, 1997 May 20 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting, 1997 May 20 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 11)
    - Board Meeting, 1997 July 10 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 12)
    - Board Meeting, 1997 July 10 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 13)
    - Board Meeting, 1997 September 16 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1)
    - Board Bi-Monthly, 1997 November 24 - 1998 September 17 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 2)
    - Board Meeting, 1997 November 24 - 1998 December 15 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 3)
    - Board Meeting, 1998 March 19 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting Script, 1998 May 21 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, 1998 May 21 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 6)
    - Board Meeting, 1998 September 17 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting Minutes and Addendum, 1999 May 13 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III.2 - Committee Minutes, 1982-2000
    The subseries contains minutes and meeting materials of the Executive Committee 1987-1998, the Personnel Committee 1989-2000, the Finance Committee 1982-2000, the Executive Council 1997, the Fund Development Committee 1988-1998, the Cultural/Recreational Committee 1989, the Capital Campaign Building Committee 1989-1992, the Facilities Property Committee 1992, the Board Program Committee 1992-1993, and the Development Committee 1990-1997, arranged in that order, and by date.
    - Executive Committee, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee, 1990 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee, 1991 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee, 1993 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee, 1994 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, 1996 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee, 1996 September 12 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee, 1996 October 15 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, 1996 November 14 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee, 1997 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee, 1997 January 9 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, 1997 February 13 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee, 1997 April 25 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, 1997 June 12 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 9)